One, two! One, two, three!
You're entering a realm
which is unusual.
Maybe it's magic
or contains some kind of monster.
The second one. Prepare to enter...
Please send the man round back
and pick up Clyde Smith,
a professional gambler who's about to have
an unfortunate accident.
A casino where I'm winning?
That car must have killed me.
I must be in heaven.
A casino where I always win?
That's boring.
I must really be in hell!
No, Mr. Smith,
you're not in heaven or hell.
You're on an airplane.
There's a gremlin destroying the plane!
You've gotta believe me!
Why should I believe you? You're Hitler!
No! Eva Braun, help me!
Ahhh!
- Saw it comin'.
- I just saw something incredibly cool,
a big floating ball that lit up
with every color in the rainbow,
plus some new ones that were so beautiful,
I fell to my knees and cried.
Was it out in front of
Discount Shoe Outlet?
Yeah.
They have a college kid
wear that to attract customers.
Well, I don't care
if it was just some dork in a costume.
For one brief moment,
I felt the heartbeat of creation,
and it was one with my own.
- Big deal.
- We all feel like that all the time,
but you don't hear us gassin' on about it.
How can you people be so blasé?
Here you are in the year 3000 or so,
yet you just sit around
like it's the boring time I came from.
"Boring"? Wasn't that the period
when they cracked the human genome
and boy bands roamed the earth?
Yeah, but now it's the distant future.
Why aren't we out
doing everything I ever dreamed of?
- Hey, you know what might be a hoot?
- No. Why would I know that?
Let's take the rest of the morning off
and take Fry to do everything
he ever wanted to do.
- Everything?
- Except that.
So's your fantasies has always been
to destroys a planet, huh?
Yeah. What did they ever do for me?
Wow. The most humdrum activities
seem almost exciting through your eyes.
- What should we do next?
- I wanna see the edge of the universe.
Ooh. That sounds cool.
It's funny. You live in the universe,
but you never do these things
till someone comes to visit.
There it is,
the edge of the universe.
Far out.
So there's an infinite number
of parallel universes?
No. Just the two.
Oh, well, I'm sure that's enough.
I'm sick of parallel Bender
lording his cowboy hat over me.
Let's move on to Fry's next fantasy.
Yee-haw!
Bow before your master, puny mortals!
Whoo! Giddy-up! Ha, ha! Whoo! Whoopie!
- Mommy? Why is that man like that?
- Don't look at him.
That was fun. Let's give him a treat.
Keep your palms flat.
The tongue tickles.
These new hands are great.
I'm gonna break 'em in tonight.
Yes, it's been quite an hour and a half.
I've only got two fantasies left,
to be invisible in a chocolate factory,
and to be romantically linked
with a celebrity.
I could pound your head
till you think that's what happened.
- Okay.
- Wait. Hold on.
It is actually possible
to meet any celebrity you want.
- It is?
- Of course.
You should read a blimp sometime.
- What part of that do I understand?
- It's simple.
You can download a celebrity's personality
and appearance into a blank robot.
Hey, I have an idea. Let's do that.
Onto the Internet you go.
Oh, and while you're there,
pick me up a few credit card numbers.
No way. Kirk could kick Picard's ass.
Yeah? At least Picard had the guts
to admit he was bald.
What? You take that back!
Ooh, eBay!
Are there no further bids
for this exquisite galaxy?
Sold to the being of inconceivable horror.
Will a money order be okay?
Yes.
So where's the celebrity dating place?
Let's search the Web.
Over there.
Welcome to nappster. Let's see
what celebrities we've got in stock.
- Can I interest you in Gwyneth Paltrow?
- Nah.
I read in Newsweek
that she drinks human blood.
How about Cleopatra,
whose beauty destroyed mighty empires?
I'd prefer someone
from the era of shaved underarms.
Do you have anything with more
of a Lucy Liu feel to it?
Nah, nothin' like that,
although we do have Lucy Liu.
Only woman to be named People magazine's
"Sexiest Woman of the Year" twice,
in 2003 and then again in 2063.
I'd like the 2003 model.
- Whoo-hoo! I found her! What do I do now?
- Download her.
Let's just put a blank robot in the drive.
It worked!
You're one sexy man...
Philip J. Fry.
It worked perfectly!
Well, you downloaded Lucy Liu.
Are you just gonna stare vacantly at her
and not say anything?
I find your slack-jawed stare
very attractive...
Philip J. Fry.
Did you hear that? She likes me.
Well, duh. She's programmed to like you.
But this is Lucy Liu, perhaps
the only good actress of the 21st century.
She's more than just a piece of software.
Would you like
to take a moment to register me?
Uh, not right now.
I'll remind you later, you hot stud you.
So, uh, what do you feel like doing?
Would you like
to take a moment to register me?
I said later.
And then when I feel so stuffed
I can't eat any more,
I just use the restroom
and then I can eat more.
You should write a book, Fry.
People need to know about the...
Can eat more.
Oh, Lucy. You're just like I always
thought you'd be from your movies.
My personality is mathematically
derived from my movies,
proportionately weighted
by box office receipts.
Whoo!
I'm just a love machine
And I won't work for nobody but you
-Yeah
-I'm just a love machine
-Yeah, baby
-A huggin', kissin' fiend
I'm just a love machine
And I won't work for nobody but you
-Yeah, baby
-I'm just a love machine
A huggin, kissin' fiend
- You're cute.
- You'recute.
- You.
Oh, dear. She's stuck in an infinite loop,
and he's an idiot.
Well, that's love for you.
Humans dating robots is sick.
You people wonder why I'm still single?
It's 'cause all the fine robot sisters
are datin' humans.
Bender, this is Fry's decision.
And he made it wrong, so it's time
for us to interfere in his life.
She doesn't really love you. She can't.
- She's just a machine that...
- Stay away from our women!
You've got metal fever, boy! Metal fever!
Well, so what if I love a robot?
It's not hurting anybody.
My God! He never took
middle school hygiene.
He never saw the propaganda film.
It's just lucky I keep a copy
in the VCR at all times.
Ordinary human dating.
It's enjoyable,
and it serves an important purpose.
But when a human dates an artificial mate,
there is no purpose, only enjoyment.
And that leads to tragedy.
Neato! A Marilyn Monroebot.
Oh, you're a real dreamboat...
Billy Everyteen.
Harmless fun? Let's see what happens next.
Billy, do you want to walk your dog?
No, thanks, Mom.
I'd rather make out with my Monroebot.
Billy, do you wanna get a paper route
and earn some extra cash?
No, thanks, Dad.
I'd rather make out with my Monroebot.
Billy, do you wanna come over tonight?
We can make out together.
Gee, Mavis, your house
is across the street.
That's an awfully long way
to go for makin' out.
Did you notice
what went wrong in that scene?
Ordinarily, Billy would work hard
to make money with his paper route.
Then he'd use the money
to buy dinner for Mavis,
thus earning a slim chance
to perform the reproductive act.
But in a world where teens
can date robots, why should he bother?
Why should anyone bother?
Let's take a look at Billy's planet
a year later.
Where are all the football stars?
And where are the biochemists?
They're trapped, trapped in the soft,
viselike grip of robot lips.
All civilization was just an effort
to impress the opposite sex
and sometimes the same sex.
Now let's skip forward
80 years into the future.
Where's Billy?
Farewell.
The next day, Billy's planet
was destroyed by aliens.
Have you guessed the name
of Billy's planet?
It was Earth!
Brought to you by...
The Space Pope
Did that make
any impression on you, Fry? Fry?
Ooh!
I knew I should've shown him
Electro-Gonorrhea:The Noisy Killer.
What is the world comin' to?
That Fry's a sicko pervert, I tell ya.
Datin' a robot,
it's an "atrocimicy."
But Fry's our friend, Bender.
Aw, geez! Will ya stifle there, meat bag?
- You stifle, Bender.
- Hooray!
Finally, you're standing up to him.
Although he is completely right.
We've got to stem
this tidal wave of moral decay.
It's time to shut down nappster.com.
- Who's in charge of this dump?
- That'd be me.
If you're an investor,
you can dump your money in the hole there.
- Listen, you fat Internet nerd.
- Listening.
Your company promotes wrong love.
If you don't shut down right now, the only
thing wired about you will be your jaw.
Yeah. You can't shut us down.
The Internet is about the free exchange
and sale of other people's ideas.
- We've done nothing wrong.
- Help! I'm being held prisoner!
Ah! Someone in trouble is.
No! Stay out. There's a... a guy goin'
for the Tetris world record in there.
Ow!
- Who are you?
- Don't hurt us.
Help me. They've been
holding me prisoner for 800 years.
The real Lucy Liu, the one you can see
a movie of in the popcorn stadium.
So what's your problem?
Those sweaty nerds
are making illegal copies of us.
Ow! It hurts!
Open this door!
Don't make me call the maintenance guy.
- It's a bluff.
- We can't take that chance.
Move, people! Move!
Please pick me up before you go-go.
She asked first.
Ahhh!
- Um... Are you Lucy Liu?
- Sure.
Oh, we're doomed!
They got the head.
They uncovered the sign.
Soon the whole world
will learn we're cyber criminals.
And we would've gotten away with it
if it weren't for those meddling adults.
We'll stop them.
They like Lucy Liu? We'll give them
all the Lucy Liu they can handle.
Hand me that backup disk.
Did you see me escaping?
I was all, like...
Woo-woo-woo
woo-woo-woo!
Thanks for rescuing me.
Especially you, Bender.
Mmm. Quite a masculine piece of metal,
aren't you?
Hey, don't look at me like that!
If you're thinkin' of crossing the line
with Bender, you can forget it.
- Bender don't bend that way.
- Hey, look.
It's another Lucy Liubot.
I am Lucy Liu. Give me your spines.
Hey, what the...
Take this and that and one of these.
Hey, cut it out.
I don't need this kind of publicity.
Ah! Oh! Ooh-ah! Ooh-ah!
Ooh-ah! Ooh-ah-ooh!
All right, Liu,
time to kick your frosty, well-toned ass.
Yaah! Whuh!
Waaa-taah!
Then along came Bender.
Looks like you're retaining water.
That was incredible, Bender.
You're like Jackie Chan
before he got all doughy.
Oh, shucks. I wasn't afraid of that robot.
I'm pretty brave
once you get past my macho exterior.
It's an army of Lucy Lius.
They're horrible.
Take this and that and one of these.
- Robot Crouching Tiger.
- Robot Crane style.
Now, that's a wave of destruction
that's easy on the eyes.
Hi-yah!
This is the best movie I've ever seen.
It has a vampire and an explosion.
It's amazing the way you...
Notice two things.
No! Don't open that coffin.
- It's ticking.
- I have to, Alex.
That coffin's not going to open itself.
Bleh!
Mmm!
Let's hide in here.
It'll add to my box office gross.
- Fry.
- Aw, you guys came to watch me make out.
That is so sweet.
Wait a second.
Is that the head of who I think it's of?
Read the jar, Evelyn Wood. Dr. Z.
Fry, a herd of Lucy Liu
are destroying the city.
- Is yours acting normally?
- Let me see.
Yep. Why do you ask?
Mr. Mayor, if you want to see
the real vampire, look in the mirror.
I can't. I'm a vampire.
Oh! Why?
And nappster says illegal copies
never hurt anybody.
Quick! This way.
Sorry, ladies. Employees only.
Oh, no! They're forming
a human pyramid of robots.
Damn it! We're weren't countin' on them
being as smart as they are sexy.
A dangerous mistake to make.
At least we've got food.
- Dr. Zoidberg, cut open that bag.
- Hooray!
And don't eat it.
Oh...
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
- Data error!
- Do not compute!
Whoo-hoo!
Life was bad, but now it's good forever.
You'll be safe in here, sweetheart.
- Get lost, Pavarotti.
- No.
Lucy Liubot, if I don't survive the corn,
I want you to know that I love you
as much as a man can love
a computerized image
of a gorgeous celebrity,
which, it turns out, is a lot.
Oh, Fry. I love you more than the moon
and the stars and the...
Poetic image number 37 not found.
What are you doing, darling? Get down!
Light hot. Oil temperature rising.
Oh, no. Malfunction.
This ain't good. System error.
You saved us.
- Are you all right?
- Yes, my love. I'll be just...
Massive corn clog in port seven.
- Are you the last copy of me?
- Yes.
- Erase her, Fry.
- What? No!
Fry, when you downloaded her
without my permission, you stole my image.
And in the end, that's all I really have.
That and the largest gold nugget
in the world, one mile in diameter.
But I just downloaded her
because I love you.
If you love the real Lucy Liu,
and not just what you've seen in movies,
genre-straddling lawyer shows,
and kiss-ass articles in People magazine,
you'll blank out that robot.
I'm sorry.
Hug me, Liubot.
I'll always remember you, Fry.
Memory deleted.
I know it hurts, buddy,
but at least you're not in a sick
relationship with a robot anymore.
Uh-huh...
And I guess now maybe
I can get to know the real Lucy Liu.
Yeah, at our wedding.
It's true. Bender and I are in love.
- But... But...
- Don't be a prude, Fry.
Boy!